A job at
the end of the world.
A salaried killer for
a big petroleum company.
I don't know why I did
half the things I've done,
but I know this
is where I belong,
surrounded by my own.
Ex-cons, fugitives,
drifters,
assholes.
Men unfit for mankind.
There's not a second
that goes by
when I'm not thinking
of you in some way.
I want to see your face,
feel your hands in mine,
feel you against me.
But I know
that will never be.
You left me,
and I can't get you back.
I move like
I imagine the damned do,
cursed.
And I feel like
it's only a matter of time.
I don't know why
I'm writing this.
I don't know
what can come of it.
I know I can't get you back.
I don't know why
this has happened to us.
I feel like it's me.
Bad luck.
Poison.
And I've stopped doing
this world any real good.
"Once more into the fray
"Into the last good fight
I'll ever know
"Live and die on this day
"Live and die on this day"
Let's go. I need your
boarding passes, please.
Please have them out.
There's a storm coming in. We
gotta get this plane off the tarmac.
You guys are fucking
this up. Let's go.
Shit. Sorry, bro.
Shit. Sorry, man. Sorry.
It is as cold as this
motherfucker's ever been, huh?
I ain't shittin'
either, man.
I stripped down
for the showers,
and icicles are
forming on my nuts.
I didn't even think
that shit was possible.
You got a girl
back in Anchorage?
No.
Oh.
I got me a few.
One had to get the scrape.
At least that's
what she told me.
She's been hitting me up
for the money ever since.
I'm like, "Bitch,
we both fucked.
"I'll split it
with you, whatever."
I'm Flannery,
by the way. Todd.
You're Ottman, right?
Ottway.
Oops, sorry, bro.
Ottway, yeah.
So, you blast critters
for a living, huh,
and do some of
that sniper shit?
What's the biggest piece of game
you've taken down? Like, a Kodiak, huh?
You know, I saw that
documentary that asshole did.
You know, the fag
who loves bears...
Listen, listen, pal. I don't
want to talk. I need some quiet.
So, I'm just going to
put my head back, okay?
Yeah, it's cool.
It's cool.
Sir. Sir, I
need you to sit down, please.
Yeah, I'm sitting.
You like that shit,
don't you?
No, I don't.
I would never
eat a sea urchin.
They say if you eat it, not
only does it make you impotent,
but it poisons you, and it
causes extreme skin reactions.
No, it's the opposite.
Plus it tastes like shit. You
ever taste that? You ever seen one?
It makes you through
with this, seriously.
What's
the other thing?
Spicy tuna roll.
Not impotent.
Oh, incontinent.
That's why you were
pissing on yourself
like you did
last Saturday night.
That reminds me
of my childhood.
No, it's a true story.
I'm a true story.
I'm playing with you, man.
Really.
And then they wash
the ammonia off the fish.
A Swedish massage.
I'm gonna be sick.
Fuck me.
Fuck.
What was that?
Shit.
Hey, guys,
do yourself a favor,
don't do that head-between-your-knees
crash position shit
if this fucker goes down.
Shut the fuck up.
Why you saying
that, man? Shut up!
Shut the fuck up.
Shut up.
Suck my dick,
Flannery.
Why would you
even say that?
I'm just saying, I seen it on the
Discovery Channel, this plane crashes,
these people's spines went
through the tops of their skulls
'cause they were all bent
over like fucking retards.
Flannery, I'm going
to knock you the fuck out.
Shut up! Who's
friends with this guy?
I'm just saying!
Stop fucking saying.
Whoever's closest,
just fucking hit him.
All right.
Fucking guy, man.
Is he planning on flying out of
this shit at any time or what?
Ooh, you boys
are sensitive.
Great, just...
Everybody stop talking.
Hey, there's ice on
this side of the window.
Please remain in your seats.
What's going on?
Hey, sweetheart?
Why is it so fucking cold
in here? Where you going?
There's ice on my window.
Miss, what's happening?
Everyone,
please remain calm.
Make sure you have
your seatbelts on.
Jesus Christ!
No, remain seated, sir.
It's too fucking cold.
Tell the pilot to get on
and tell us what's going on here.
I know that's not
supposed to happen.
Sir, you have to sit
back down in your seat!
Fucking crazy!
I'm gonna die!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
Help me, somebody!
Help!
Somebody help me! Fuck.
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
We fucking went down!
Oh, my God.
That guy's cut in half.
What the fuck!
Don't look! Don't look at it.
Don't look! Look at me.
Look at me! We went down.
My hand's fucked,
my leg's fucked.
Ah! Fuck!
It's good.
It's good that it hurts.
Is it good?
It's good, yeah.
Then I'm fucking fabulous.
Yeah. Are you
bleeding anywhere else?
I don't know, man.
I can't tell.
Let me get you some cover.
Don't go. Don't leave me.
No, no! I'll be straight
back. Where are you going?
It's okay.
I'll be straight back.
Fuck. Shit.
Ottway!
I gotta
get out of here.
It's gonna be okay.
There's some
Vicodin in my bag.
Hernandez.
Hernandez, you okay?
I just gotta make a call to
Vanessa. I gotta make a quick call.
Quick, to Vanessa.
Just one call.
You're in shock,
Hernandez.
But I need you to
stand up and help me.
What happened?
The plane went down, man.
What?
We crashed.
No, no, no way.
That's bullshit.
That's fucking bullshit.
I'm just asleep.
We crashed.
I was just sleeping.
Like, there's no way
that could've happened.
What about the pilots?
The pilots?
What are you talking about?
The plane's gone, man.
It's in pieces.
Look.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
This is so fucked up.
I can't fucking
believe it.
Is there a bunch
of people dead?
Yes.
Now I need you to help me
find the ones that aren't.
Come on. Can you walk?
Yeah.
Come on...
Told me to come out...
It's fucking freezing.
You know what, homes?
Fuck!
I can't feel my fingers.
Help me.
I got you, Flannery.
I got you.
Diaz. Diaz. Diaz.
Excuse me
for a second?
Watch your head.
No.
No. This is too much.
- It's just too much coming out of it.
- Come on, fuck!
I wish one of these
fucking phones would work!
I got you some help.
It's just... I'm losing too much blood.
I can't lose
all this blood.
Help him.
Ottway, help him.
This can't be
all coming outside.
Too much blood.
This is way too much blood.
Fuck.
Ottway, help me, okay?
Something's wrong. Something's
really, really wrong here.
Okay? I don't feel right.
I just don't...
Ottway, okay,
this doesn't...
Look. I know. Okay.
It don't feel right.
Something feels
really fucking wrong.
Listen, listen.
You're gonna die.
That's what's happening.
It's okay.
No.
No. No.
No, no, no. Wait,
wait, wait. Hold on.
Hold on!
It's okay.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Look at me.
Keep looking at me.
It's all right.
Look at me.
Keep looking at me.
It's all right.
It'll slide over you.
It'll start to feel warm.
Nice and warm.
Let it move over you.
It's all right.
What?
Let your thoughts go.
All the good things.
All the good
things. Yeah?
Who do you love?
Who do you love, Luke?
My girl Rosie.
Is she
your daughter?
She's six.
Let her take you, then.
Let her take you.
It's okay. It's okay.
Wait for me.
Did he
just fucking die?
He just fucking died,
didn't he?
Come on.
Did you...
Yeah.
Did you feel him go?
I felt him go.
Is this everyone?
Is this everyone
who's still alive?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
One, two, three...
Seven. Seven of us
that we know of. Yeah?
Okay. Okay.
You happy, fuckhead?
You had to open up your fat fucking
mouth. You had to keep talking.
You had to put
the whammy on us.
I didn't do shit. Did
I fucking crash us? Huh?
We need a fire.
Did I...
I didn't do shit.
We should gather up
anything that'll burn,
seats, luggage,
any wood we can find.
What are you doing?
I said we need a fire.
It's about 10 below
and dropping.
So we don't die.
We build up a fire,
then we find food.
And at daybreak, we figure
out what way is south,
and we start walking.
Nobody's gonna find us.
Not here.
Somebody will find us. I mean,
somebody'll be fucking searching.
They gotta know that
plane went off the radar.
Right. If they send 50
planes, maybe they'll find us.
But they won't send 50 planes
because it won't matter.
Because we won't
have time to wait
for the one or two
that they will send.
Corporate doesn't give a fuck.
Nobody gives a shit
about us.
You know how much payroll they
just pocketed in this crash?
If we don't move and work
now, we're all fucked.
Unless you want
to freeze to death,
'cause that's the one thing
that will come for you.
Hey, asshole! That's jet
fuel, get away from there.
Water, wood,
something to wear.
Hey, you can't burn that.
That shit'll kill us.
Fuck.
Ohh.
We gotta do
something with the bodies.
Fuck the bodies.
The bodies...
Grab what burns.
Or you're gonna be a body.
Relax, Rambo. Relax.
You fucking relax.
Tell me to relax.
They're everywhere.
I got a book.
It's called We're All
Fucked! It's a bestseller.
Here you go.
Fuck.
Hey, man. Take it easy with that. Why?
'Cause I don't wanna
fucking catch fire.
Hello?
I see you! I'm coming.
Jesus Christ.
Get off her,
you motherfucker.
Where are they?
You okay?
You see them?
I swear, these motherfuckers...
Is there any more?
Hey, man. We gotta get
the fuck out of here.
Don't stand around.
Let's get
the fuck out.
Fuck this! Do not stand
the fuck in one place.
You fucking
kidding me?
Ottway, what the
hell was that?
- What was that?
- What the hell was that?
Did you fucking
see that? Coyotes?
I didn't see it.
I heard it.
I didn't see shit!
They're fucking big.
They're big.
Maybe I'll turn into
a wolf man now, huh?
Wait, that shit's
not real, right?
You mean, he can't...
Asswipe, what do
you think? Really?
I don't know, man. I meant,
like, rabies or whatever.
I didn't think
the motherfucker was
gonna grow claws
and teeth and shit.
Fuck.
So, you think
there's more of them?
Wolves? Maybe.
Yeah. Most likely.
But we shouldn't be worrying
about them right now.
We should be worrying
about finding food.
They're probably
only passing through.
Wait a minute. Passing
through as opposed to what?
Living here. Hunting here.
Wolves have a territorial
range of about 300 miles,
and a kill range of 30.
If we're close to their den,
and if we're within that radius,
then they'll come after us.
Well, how can we
tell if we're close?
We can't.
They might've
just been feeding.
There's bodies everywhere. I
threatened them, they attacked.
What about
the radius?
I mean, if we're in that,
what? They're gonna fight us?
I thought wolves
were scared of people.
Not if we're
near their den.
They're not scared
of anything then.
What kind of
wolves are they?
I mean, what do they call the
ones that just eat plants and shit?
They don't
call them wolves.
Herbivores,
that's what you mean.
That's wishful thinking.
When did you become king shit
fucking animal expert all of a sudden?
They paid me to kill those things,
to keep them from killing you.
So it makes sense for me
to know they're man-eaters
and they don't give a shit
about berries and shrubs.
There's blood in the air.
And there's death.
They know we're wounded.
They can smell it.
Hopefully they
won't fuck with us.
We need to move
these bodies out of here.
And then we've
gotta find food.
Check this
fucking thing out.
Jesus, Diaz,
don't do that.
No, man.
I saw one of these once.
It's got a beacon, you know?
Like a GPS.
Yeah.
Holy shit!
Holy shit, man.
It works. It's beeping!
This thing will reach up,
like, 40,000 feet!
Yes, I think that's
great that that gives you hope.
It's fucking
heartwarming.
Very funny, bro.
That's nice, my friend. That's
calfskin. It's very nice. Not cheap.
Since you cocksuckers didn't
give us a holiday bonus,
I'm gonna accept this
on behalf of my homies.
Put that back.
Put it back!
We're not looting
dead bodies for swag.
You got lucky
today, Ottway.
You should be lying there
with them. Don't push it.
I'm not gonna
say it again.
Motherfucker,
take a big step back!
I'm gonna start beating the shit
out of you in the next five seconds,
and you're gonna swallow a lot
of blood for a fucking billfold.
I can't fucking
stand guys like that.
Hey, you're gonna just
turn that into charcoal, bro.
No, I got it.
By my account, I'd say
we have about enough booze
for you guys to get
drunk two more times.
Don't get weird.
After that,
then we'll all be sober.
Jack makes me fight.
Oh, yeah.
Ladies, ladies!
You like the white
or the brown?
How about
some brown stuff?
No tequila.
Sorry about that.
It's all good.
Thanks, papa.
Where the fuck
did you get that?
In that thing, that
serving thing with wheels on it.
Bunch of dead
bodies all over, man.
You wanna make sure you know
where that meat came from.
It's like that movie where they start
taking chunks of frozen
ass out of that guy.
The plane crash.
That dude from Training Day? Right.
That'd be fucking
funny as fuck.
That was like
dead ass on a stick.
Or you thought like a severed
dick was a hotdog, right?
That's
too fucking funny.
I wish some of the other
dudes would have lived.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You hear that?
Get up! Get up!
What is that?
Go, go, go!
What the fuck is that?
What is it?
What the fuck...
Everybody be cool.
Don't move.
Jesus Christ!
Stare right back
at them.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why are they coming closer?
Fuck this shit. I'm
getting back in the plane.
Flannery, God damn it, don't move.
Look at the size of
that fucking thing.
We'll take...
We'll take two-hour shifts.
I'll start.
You guys get some sleep.
Yeah, like that
shit's gonna happen.
Don't be afraid.
Hey.
Don't drift off on us, Burke.
I'll be all right.
I'm not going to sleep.
Oh, you motherfucker.
Where is my goddamn kid
when I need him?
Fuck it.
Fuck.
Oh, Jesus, God.
Hey. Hey!
No, no, no, no.
Fuck!
Hernandez!
Shit!
They ate him.
Jesus Christ.
They weren't
eating him.
They were killing him.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
How did we not hear him?
How many did it
take to do that?
We could dig in, make some kind
of a stand. Not much cover, though.
Whoa, whoa,
what do you mean "stand"?
Like, fight those motherfucking
giant things? You out of your mind?
They'll get bold. And
start to come in for us.
Why would they? I mean, we're not
harming them. It's not for food.
We're a threat. We don't
belong here. That's it.
There's trees out there.
If we could get to that tree
line, they might back off.
If they see that we're
leaving, they might.
Fuck that! What they might do, bullshit.
What they might do? Are
you fucking kidding me?
Hey. They pissed
all over this place.
They mean to tag it. We can't
wait them out, we'll starve.
There's a lot of bad space
between us and that forest,
but if we get
there, then...
We can better
defend ourselves.
Less exposed,
I don't know.
Yeah, you don't know.
And nobody nominated
you shit, by the way.
It's getting to that
point in the evening, girls.
Fucking to
each his own.
What the fuck you talking
about. Diaz? Come on, man.
You wouldn't last five
fucking minutes out here.
I survived that.
This ain't shit.
I'd find a way through,
with or without you.
Fuck it. I'm gonna take whatever I
can carry and head into those trees.
If you guys wanna join me,
I'd strip everything.
Fuck. All right,
let's fucking do this.
Hey.
We should collect
all the wallets
for the families.
Wallets? Did I hear wallets?
I'll carry the wallets.
Henrick?
Do you mind carrying them?
Yeah, let's waste
a little more time.
Even though the weather's
about to kick our ass.
You grab them wallets.
Fucking idiots.
To Hernandez.
Grab as many
as you can.
Waste as much
fucking time as you can.
I'm gonna sit here with
my friend, Jack Daniel's,
and waste some time
of my own.
Why don't you just
fucking help us, man?
I'm helping you. I'm helping
you. I'm warming up, man.
You guys find any rubbers,
save them.
I don't know how long I'm gonna
be out here with you fairies.
Why don't you
shut the fuck up?
Key to survival, fellas,
getting them wallets.
Getting them wallets.
Henrick.
Wait.
I feel like we
should say something.
I mean, all these bodies,
all these...
All these people that died, it
doesn't seem right to just walk away.
I don't know any
official prayers, so, I guess...
God bless these men.
They were,
some of them, our friends, and
we could be lying here with them.
So thank you for sparing
us and helping us.
Oh, and keep that up
if you can.
Fuck!
Don't worry about me,
motherfuckers!
You know, you wanna run off
into the trees, that's cool, too!
No, no, no, no. Ottway!
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
Fuck! Flannery!
Get off him!
Flannery!
Get away from him!
Jesus.
Flannery! Flannery!
Get off him!
No.
Do you wanna say anything?
Come on, let's keep moving. There's
nothing else we can do for him.
Those trees aren't
getting any fucking closer.
We're gonna be out here
in the dark with those things.
We have no idea
if we're going toward
the den or away
from it, do we?
Why didn't we just
stay with the plane?
Come on. They
would have surrounded us.
How the fuck do we know
they're not doing that right now?
Fucking genius.
We're still
better off in the trees.
Yeah, we're better off.
Go tell that kid, you fuck.
Hey, what is that?
Run!
Go! Go!
Get into the trees!
Mother of Christ!
Go, go, go!
Jesus,
they're right on us!
Don't stop moving!
Wait, wait,
wait! Wait!
Don't look back!
Run! Run!
They're flanking us!
Don't stop!
You see them?
They're all around us.
We need a fire to
keep them off us. Hurry!
The wood's wet.
Whole thing's wet.
Hurry, hurry!
Get that
fucking thing lit.
- Come on!
- Come on, baby, come on.
Tell me that
thing's not broke.
Damn this thing.
Just
get it going, Ottway.
Light! Light!
That's it,
that's it.
It's going out.
Fuck!
Jesus, come on!
Smother...
Don't smother it.
It worked.
We should start
perimeter fires.
Let's see these bastards
before they come for us.
What the fuck
was that?
The alpha. They went at him.
He put it down.
Whatever that challenge was,
the alpha put it down.
How are we gonna
deal with this?
We kill them,
one at a time.
Tip the numbers. That's
what they're doing to us.
What the hell are these for?
I'll explain.
Friction tape,
electrical tape.
Talget, you had
some, yeah?
It's in there somewhere.
Shotgun shell.
Spear tip.
The tip has to drive into the
primer to set off the shell.
Secure them
with these sticks,
a little bit of
tape, simple.
You jab with it when
the wolf gets close.
Hit them hard.
Let it get real close.
It'll work.
It's like a bang stick.
The round discharges,
you pull it loose,
you still got something
sharp to create distance.
Unless you wanna
fist fight them.
There you go.
One shot a piece, guys.
Make them count. Burke.
Blacken the tips
in the fire, guys.
It makes them harder,
stronger.
Really, boys?
This is what it's
come down to, huh?
This MacGyver bullshit?
Okay.
Good.
I appreciate a good laugh
as much as the next guy.
These things,
they see well at night?
Jesus, can we talk about
something else, please?
Talget, you're carrying all
that booze. Let's break it out.
I recommend
rationing what we have.
I recommend you
kissing my ass.
What are you,
the booze police now?
You fucking guys with your rules
and your orders and bullshit.
Where are we?
Look around.
This is Fucked City,
population five and dwindling.
Two days, three maybe, if we
really pull our shit together.
And who's in charge of that
right now? This fucking guy?
The Great White hunter?
And his jerry-rigged
fucking wolf sticks?
Why are you constantly breaking
balls and bitching about everything?
'Cause I wanna live,
motherfucker. You understand that?
I don't want some timber wolf
shitting me out on this mountain.
You're scared.
What?
You don't need all that nonsense,
all that chest-puff bullshit.
What's wrong
with being scared?
I'm not scared.
You're not?
No.
I'm terrified.
I can tell.
And not an ounce of
shame in saying it.
I'm scared shitless.
That's because
you're a punk.
I don't walk through this
world with fear in my heart.
You picked that up
in the pen?
Somebody scribble that
on the day room wall?
You better take it easy,
motherfucker.
Talking tough means jack
shit now. You're not scared?
You're a fool.
Worse, you're a fucking liar.
I should have checked your
chin at the fucking plane.
Get up, come on,
get up, you big Irish fuck.
You wanna knuckle up... Hey,
Diaz, put the fucking knife away.
We don't have time for this.
Get the fuck off me!
Hey, Diaz, put
the knife away. Shut up!
Shut up, you chickenshits make me sick.
Son of a bitch!
You got that kid
Flannery killed
and you're not
gonna get me killed.
Put your fucking hands up. Let
me show you how this is done.
Put your fucking hands up.
Fuck! You motherfucker!
You cut this shit out.
Do you hear me?
Get up,
get up, get up.
What the fuck?
What did it want?
You.
Diaz, please don't do
that shit to me again.
All right?
No mas.
It was bullshit.
I'm sorry.
I'm so...
Get it off! Get it off!
Fuck!
Bite me, you fuck!
Come here, you fuck!
Fuck!
Hey, Diaz,
I think you got him.
Yeah!
You fuck! Fuck!
I think I lost
a nail.
Is that the big one?
That big fucker?
It's not the alpha.
It's an omega, an outcast.
They sent it in to test
you, Diaz.
Did I pass, bitch?
Did I fucking pass?
You fucking dog.
Let's get a large branch,
sharpen the end of it,
shove it up
this thing's ass.
We're gonna cook
this son of a bitch.
And then we're gonna eat it.
Hey, wolf,
not so tough now, huh, wolf?
You want it?
No.
Come on. I got it, I got it. I don't...
Is this the white
meat or the dark meat?
Make it as black as
possible. Put it there.
Yeah? I know it tastes
like shit but, guys,
it might be the last meat
we'll get for a while.
It's gristly, too.
- It tastes like shit, I know, but eat it, guys.
- Yeah.
It tastes like dog shit.
And I'm much more of
a cat person, really.
Burke?
Yeah?
You all right?
My head's a
little off. I'm...
Sit down, sit down.
...feeling a little dizzy.
That's it.
You think they're
watching us?
Yeah, they're watching us.
You fuck with us
and we'll fuck with you.
You hear that?
You're not the animals!
We're the animals!
Come here, you fucker.
Come here, you puppy.
Oh, yeah.
You're a twisted fuck. You're
wrong for that. That is wrong.
Nothing's fucking... I'm not
crazy. I'm not fucking crazy.
You fuck.
That's fucked up.
I mean,
that's fucked up.
Ah, you try to steal
my fucking life.
Come on, you fuck.
You hear the bones cracking,
Diaz. Come on, that's enough.
Fucking mutt. Come on.
Let him have this.
Little Fido here
wants to go home.
Wants to see his brothers.
Jesus Christ. Stop.
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna help him get there.
Say goodbye, boys.
Take him back,
motherfucker!
We should
keep moving.
Those goddamn things
are calling us out.
What the hell are
you talking about, Talget?
Wolves are the only animal
that will seek revenge.
Hey, I don't want to hear
any more about the fucking wolves,
or you're gonna start
seeing them everywhere.
Burke,
how are you doing?
I can't breathe.
I can't keep going.
Ottway,
we can't keep going.
We can't stop.
Those things will be all
over us. We gotta keep going.
Ottway,
Burke is hurting here, man.
This will work.
It's a dead end.
They can't get in
behind us.
They'll have to hit us
from out front.
Let's build a fire.
That thing still working?
Up to 40,000 feet.
This shit had to save
somebody at some point, right?
I keep
sitting here thinking.
Even with all
this stuff going on,
we hit the ground
at 400 miles an hour,
and we made it.
Why would we go through
something like that, that crash,
if it wasn't meant to be,
or ordained?
By who?
The Almighty?
That fucking fairy tale?
How about good
old-fashioned blind luck?
Flannery survived that
crash, so did Hernandez.
It don't matter.
Fate doesn't give a fuck.
Dead is dead.
Where do you think
those boys are now?
Up in heaven?
Being fitted for wings?
No, I'll tell you
where they are.
They're not. That's where.
They're nowhere.
They're gone.
No, I don't believe it.
I do.
I wish I didn't.
I really wish I could
believe in that stuff.
This is real, the cold.
That's real.
The air in my lungs.
Those bastards out there
in the dark stalking us.
It's this world that I'm worried
about, Talget, not the next.
What about your faith?
What about it?
It's important.
Emma?
Is she with you guys?
It's okay, big guy.
She's was at the back.
I was speaking with her.
She's...
She's not here.
Yeah, she's not here yet.
Why don't you...
You tell her
that I'm here.
Of course, yeah. Just
lie down, she's coming.
Emma's coming. Yeah.
He's seeing things?
He's hallucinating.
It's hypoxia.
Not enough oxygen's
getting to his brain.
Hypoxia.
Why don't the rest
of us have it?
It depends on the person. Some
people can't handle the altitude.
Who's Emma?
She was his sister.
She died
when he was a kid.
My daughter, Mary.
She's got really long hair
almost down to her waist.
In fact, it's the one rule
my fucking ex respects,
which is that I'm the
only one who cuts her hair.
She does this thing. She'll
come and hover over me.
I'll just be dead asleep,
and she'll start swinging
her head back and forth,
tickling me with
her hair all in my face,
and she'll be
laughing like crazy.
It's a certain type
of laugh, you know,
when the kid goes past
laughing to laughing, like a...
You know, like you
can't really breathe,
sounding more like
an old man than a kid.
I miss the hell
out of that kid.
Yeah.
You should.
You know that?
Those things from your life,
whatever they might be,
make you want that next
minute more than the last.
Make you fight for it.
I just wanna
fuck one more time.
See, you ruined
my story, motherfucker.
No. No, man.
I'm telling a nice little
sweet story about my daughter...
I don't mean to
wreck your shit.
I know, I know.
I just can't go out on that last
piece of horrible ass that I had.
You know what I'm saying? A
53-year-old hooker, half-Eskimo.
We shouldn't
talk about that.
She was 250, 260.
No shit.
The bitch gave me the clap
like it was gift wrapped.
No, no, no.
Anyway...
No, I just think
that I would punch out
and that would be my
fucking swan song, right?
That alone
is worth the fight.
That's worth the fight.
My...
My dad was not
without love...
Why didn't we catch...
Not ready to.
Drinker, brawler,
all that stuff.
Never shed a tear.
Saw weakness everywhere.
But he had this thing
for poems, poetry,
reading them, quoting them.
Probably thought it
rounded him off, you know.
His way of apologizing,
I guess.
And there was one that hung
over the desk in his den.
It was only when I was a lot
older, I realized he had written it.
It was untitled, four lines.
I read it at his funeral.
"Once more into the fray
"Into the last good fight
I'll ever know
"Live and die on this day
"Live and die on this day"
Storm clouds.
Blizzard?
A good bet.
Based on our luck,
it's a fucking lock.
Let's bundle Burke up
and dig in against these trees.
The snow's deep enough.
I'm worried if we lose
this fire, we'll all freeze.
Burke, wake up!
Come on. Move your arms!
Let me see you move
your arms! Come on, move!
Burke, wake up! Burke,
you big bastard! Wake up!
Don't sleep, you hear me?
Don't sleep! Wake up!
Come on, Burke!
Burke, come on,
wake up! Burke!
Burke! Burke! Wake up!
Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up, bugger! Wake up.
Don't be afraid.
What is it?
Guys, get up. Up.
Is it them?
Saw marks.
These trees
have been logged.
That's water.
That sounds like a river.
You gotta be
shitting me.
The river must be a good size
if we can hear it all the way up here.
At least if
we're following a river,
we got a better chance
of finding shelter.
Who's climbing
down that?
I can't.
There's no way I can do that.
Well,
we can't go back.
There's no way
we can go back.
Those trees, though.
What trees?
Right over there.
Get a tether of some kind,
secure it between here and
there, we can climb down.
Guys, it's simple.
It's the wolves
or those trees.
You're not talking
about jumping off the cliff?
It's an idea. I
didn't say it was a good one.
He's talking about
jumping off the cliff.
This will wind up being one of
those wild stories you tell at a party,
pretty girl on your lap.
All right.
Are you ready?
Yeah, why not?
Don't get a good running
start, get a great one.
Now you'll freefall
about 30 feet,
but it's gonna
feel like 30,000.
Is this supposed to
pass for a pep talk?
When we feel this go taut,
we'll take up the slack
to stop you from
hitting too hard.
You get in there.
I'll figure it out.
If you gotta go, this is a
pretty cool way to go, bro.
Better a flying leap
than those fucking wolves.
I hope there's
something down there.
Fuck.
Go! Go, go! Go! Go!
Fuck!
Which one of you fuckers...
Grab him! Grab him!
Pull me up!
Fuck, pull me back!
Henrick?
Henrick, you in there?
Yeah!
I'm all right!
Anyone with
an urge to go first?
Talget? Diaz?
I'll go.
Don't stay
out there too long.
Henrick!
Make sure that
thing is secure!
It's secure, but I don't
know how long it's gonna last!
Don't spend a lot
of time out there!
You all right?
You go.
What about your hand?
I'm all right.
Go ahead, just haul me in
if anything goes wrong.
Yeah.
I just fucking hate heights,
man. It flips me out.
Well, then you go,
I'll stay and make sure...
No, no. I'm good.
You cross.
Seriously, give me a minute,
get my head around it.
All right,
I'm through! I'm across!
I'm coming!
All right,
I'm coming across now.
Okay.
Come on, you can do this.
You can do this.
Come on.
Talget, are you ready?
Talget, stop
fucking around!
Move your ass!
Talget!
Hey, baby girl.
I love you, Daddy.
No, God, no!
They're fucking
killing him!
Get to him!
Go! Go!
Go... Get down there!
They're taking him!
Talget!
They fucking took him.
No, no!
Ow! Fuck! Ah!
Talget!
They took him.
They fucking took him.
My knee.
My fucking knee.
They're just
picking us off one by one.
I'm fucked.
I'm fucked. My knee!
Let's get you up.
I can't...
I can't. Fuck!
Get up.
Fucking things.
They're not gonna
let us go, are they?
What do you do?
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck.
Forget it.
Whatever I had in the tank,
I used back there.
I'm beat.
I just wanna sit.
I just wanna
stop this bullshit.
Fucking leg.
My ankle's fucked.
Diaz, don't sit down.
Don't sit down.
I know. I know.
I don't wanna argue.
I just wanna rest.
I just had
the clearest thought.
I'm done.
Come on, man. Up.
There could be a cabin
downriver right there.
That's a mile up,
at least, brother.
I can't walk that, man.
I can't walk 50 feet.
Fuck it.
I gave it a shot.
What the fuck, man?
Are you serious?
I really thought this
fucking watch would work.
Does it slide over you?
You told Lewenden back in the
plane that it slides over you.
Death.
That it was warm.
Is that true?
Yeah.
We carry him.
We put a litter together
and slide him down the banks.
I'm not going
anywhere, Henrick.
I don't want to.
I don't need to.
What the fuck is
wrong with you?
Is that it? You're just gonna
sit there? Is that what you want?
Yeah.
After what we survived?
That's exactly why.
What I got waiting
for me back there?
I'm gonna sit on
a drill all day.
Get drunk all night.
That's my life?
Turn around
and look at that.
I feel like
that's all for me.
How do I beat that?
When would it
ever be better?
I can't explain it.
I don't have
the words, brother.
My first name
is John.
My first name is Pete.
Pete.
You look like a Pete.
John Ottway.
Of course that's your name.
Thank you, John.
Thank you.
Luck.
I'm not afraid.
Can I ask
you something?
Yeah.
Where were you
going that night?
That last night in camp.
Get the fuck out of here!
At the bar.
You had your rifle,
you went out...
My shift.
No.
You worked that morning,
I remember.
I went out, yeah.
With your rifle.
Did you follow me?
No.
But I never thought
I'd see you alive again.
Back there with Diaz.
That look he had.
I've only seen
it one other time.
On you.
That last night in camp.
It really doesn't
matter now, does it?
No, I don't suppose
it does.
Henrick, run. Run!
Henrick!
Henrick.
Henrick, move on.
Come on.
What the fuck are you doing?
Hold your breath.
God damn it,
hold your breath.
Jesus. Please,
don't do this.
Do something.
You phony, prick,
fraudulent motherfucker.
Do something!
Come on! Prove it!
Fuck faith, earn it!
Show me something real.
I need it now. Not later, now.
Show me, and I'll believe
in you till the day I die.
I swear. I'm calling on you.
I'm calling on you!
Fuck it. I'll do it myself.
I'll do it myself.
A den.
It's their fucking den.
Don't be afraid.
"Once more into the fray
"Into the last good
fight I'll ever know
"Live and die on this day
"Live and die
"on this day"